erevollution.com 2016-10-30

# eRevollution

**INTRODUCTION**  
We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. By accessing any of the eRevollution sites, you are consenting to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy describes:

  * what information eRevollution collects from users;
  * how such information is used and stored;
  * when such information may be disclosed to third parties;
  * how users, parents, and guardians can control the use and disclosure of collected information;
  * and how information is protected.

**INFORMATION THAT WE MAY COLLECT**  
eRevollution collects only the information that is reasonably necessary for the activities available on the particular website. In general, we collect e-mail addresses.

**USE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION**  
We may use your e-mail address to uniquely identify you as a user of eRevollution. Subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy, we may use your contact information to process our newsletters and/or e-mail campaigns.  
In general the information we collect may be used to:

  * respond to your requests,
  * measure analytics;
  * and manage and improve the services available on eRevollution

**INFORMATION WE SHARE WITH THIRD PARTIES.**  
Depending upon the circumstances, we may share collected information with:

  * law enforcement or others as needed to protect or defend our rights and the rights of others,
  * third parties we hire to handle certain activities;
  * otherwise with your permission

We will not share your information with any third parties, except that you may disclose your personal information to third parties who perform services for us, such as PayPal system.  
Those third parties have access to your information only as necessary to perform their functions, and for no other purposes.

**YOUR CONTROL OVER INFORMATION.**  
You have the right to access, update and correct factual inaccuracies in any personally identifiable information we collect about you. You can...

  * stop the delivery of commercial e-mail messages from eRevollution by following the instructions in e-mails

**SECURITY OF COLLECTED INFORMATION**  
HOW WE STORE SUCH INFORMATION.  
We store your information using reasonable security precautions and for only as long as we think reasonably necessary. eRevollution takes all reasonable precautions to...

  * safeguard the privacy of your data. All data that we collect is stored on one or more secure database servers that cannot be accessed from outside All employees of eRevollution are legally bound by a non disclosure agreement that prevents the disclosure of any corporate or customer information to other parties.

**COOKIES:**  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we may transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. We use cookies to enhance your online experience.  
The Help portion of the toolbar on most Web browsers will tell you:

  * how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies,
  * how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie,
  * how to entirely disable

However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of eRevollution essential features, we recommend that you leave cookies turned on.

**CONTACT US:**  
To review, modify or remove the information you have provided to us, or to contact us with any questions or complaints, please e-mail us at erevollutiongame@gmail.com

**AGREEMENT WITH eRevollution GAMES POLICIES**  
By accessing and/or using any of eRevollution offerings, you signify your understanding of and agreement with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our policies, please do not access or use any eRevollution offerings.

**CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**  
We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "last modified" date at the top of this page. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how eRevollution protects your information. If you continue using any of eRevollution offerings it means that you are accepting this Privacy Policy with the modifications.
